verticalsearchworks.com 2011-12-08

# Vertical Search Works - Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the VerticalSearchWorks Web site (the “VSW Web site”). The protection of privacy is important to VSW Corporation, its affiliates and subsidiaries (“VSW”). To better protect privacy, VSW provides this notice explaining VSW’s online information practices and the choices a User can make about the way information is collected and used at this site.

### What information does the VSW Web site collect?

The primary purpose of the VSW Web site is to provide VSW’s customers, prospective customers, partners, stockholders, the investment community and the public (“Users”) information about VSW. From time to time, VSW may invite Users to subscribe to an email service, order products, enter contests, and vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, among other things. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about User interests in and use of various products, programs, and services. The VSW Web site also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when Users visit many of VSW’s Web site pages such as the type of browser a User is using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system a User is using, (e.g., Windows ’95 or Mac OS) and the domain name of a User’s Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink).

### How does the VSW Web site use the information?

The VSW Web site may use the information the User provides about a User to fulfill the User’s requests for VSW’s products, programs, and services, to respond to the User’s inquiries about VSW’s software products and services, and to offer the User other products, programs or services that VSW believes may be of interest to the User. VSW sometimes uses this information to communicate with the User, such as to notify the User when the User has won one of VSW’s contests, to fulfill a request by a User to receive information by email, or to contact a User about VSW’s products and services. The VSW Web site sometimes uses the non-personally identifiable information that the VSW Web site collects to improve the design and content of VSW’s site and to enable us to personalize a User’s Internet experience. The VSW Web site also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage. Under certain circumstances, VSW may disclose personally identifiable information to third parties. VSW may disclose personally identifiable information, for example, in response to legal process in response to a court order or a subpoena. VSW also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request. Agents and contractors of VSW who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for VSW. Although VSW takes appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, the VSW Web site cannot assure Users that personally identifiable information that the VSW Web site collects will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. From time to time the VSW Web site may disclose personally identifiable information to companies whose practices are not covered by this privacy notice that want to market products or services to a User. If the VSW Web site shares personally identifiable information to such a third party, VSW will provide Users with an opportunity to opt out or block such uses. The VSW Web site may on occasion combine information the VSW Web site received online with outside records to enhance VSW’s ability to market to Users those products or services that may be of interest to Users. If Users prefer to not receive marketing information from this site, please follow the Opt-Out Procedures set forth below. Finally, VSW will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing Users with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.

### Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors

The VSW Web site may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than VSW’s. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy policies because the VSW Web site has no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. The VSW Web site may sometimes offer content (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, or promotions) that is sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. VSW has no control over these third parties’ use of this information.

### Cookies

To enhance User experience with VSW’s sites, the VSW Web site may employ “cookies.” Cookies are text files the VSW Web site places in its User computer’s browser to store User preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us the User e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless the User chooses to provide this information to us by, for example, registering for a VSW Web site promotion. Once a User chooses to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. VSW primarily uses cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content of the VSW Web site. For example, VSW may use cookies to personalize a User’s experience at the VSW Web site or save a User password in password-protected areas. The VSW Web site also may use cookies to offer the User VSW products, promotions, or services.

### Security

The VSW Web site has security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under VSW’s control. Any time the VSW Web site asks for a credit card number, the VSW Web site transmits that credit card number in an encrypted format. The VSW Web site uses industry-standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be secure. As a result, while the VSW Web site strives to protect User personal information, VSW cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information Users transmit to or from VSW’s online products or services, and Users do so at their own risk. Once the VSW Web site receives a User transmission, VSW will make reasonable efforts to ensure its security on VSW’s systems.

### Children

The VerticalSearchWorks Web site is a general audience site. It is not intended for, nor does VSW direct any of its content to, children under thirteen (13) years of age.

### Opt-Out Procedures

VSW gives a User the following options for removing User information from VSW’s database in order to stop receiving future communications from VSW. (Please note: VSW is not responsible for removing information from third-party lists or entities with which a User has previously authorized us to share its User information.)

  1. You can send email to: [info@verticalsearchworks.com](mailto:info@verticalsearchworks.com)
  2. You can send mail to the following postal address:  
VSW Corporation, Corporate Headquarters  
1919 Gallows Road, Suite 1050, Vienna, Virginia 22182
  3. You can call the following telephone number: 703.761.3700

### Contacting VSW

If users have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or other matters relating to the VSW Web site, please feel free to contact: [info@verticalsearchworks.com  
](mailto:info@verticalsearchworks.com)  
VSW Corporation  
1919 Gallows Road, Suite 1050  
Vienna, Virginia 22182

Any of the policies or procedures above may be changed at any time without prior notice. Although this Privacy Policy is not a binding contract and does not create any legal rights, it does serve as an expression of VSW’s commitment to protecting private personal information.
